<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A Letter sent by a gentleman of England to his frende contayning a confutacion of a French mans errors, in the report of the myraculous starre nowe shyninge.</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1573</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 11 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 7 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2011-04">2011-04 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A05372</idno>
            <idno type="STC">STC 15525.3</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC S2177</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">23106732</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 23106732</idno>
            <idno type="VID">26242</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A05372)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 26242)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1475-1640 ; 1797:29)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A Letter sent by a gentleman of England to his frende contayning a confutacion of a French mans errors, in the report of the myraculous starre nowe shyninge.</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[12] p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>By Thomas Marshe,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1573.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Place of publication and publisher from colophon.</note>
                  <note>Signatures: A⁸(-A1, last leaf blank).</note>
                  <note>Illustrated t.p.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the Lambeth Palace Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Astronomy --  Early works to 1800.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2009-12</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2009-12</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-02</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-02</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-04</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:26242:1"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 99 -->
            <pb facs="tcp:26242:1"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 99 -->
            <p>
               <hi>A LETTER</hi> ſent by a Gentleman of England, <hi>to his frende, contayning a confutacion</hi> of a French mans errors, in the report <hi>of the myraculous ſtarre nowe</hi> ſhyninge.</p>
            <figure>
               <figDesc>symbolic celestial configuration</figDesc>
            </figure>
            <p>Anno Domini. 1573.</p>
            <figure/>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="letter">
            <pb facs="tcp:26242:2"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 100 -->
            <pb facs="tcp:26242:2"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 100 -->
            <opener>
               <salute>Miſopſeudolugos Philomathei, Salutem.</salute>
            </opener>
            <p>
               <seg rend="decorInit">S</seg>Ir, whereas ye requyre my opynion touching y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> French Pamflet of a blaſing ſtarre lately Engliſhed: Surely I cannot but condempne y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> raſhnes of him that did tranſlate y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> ſame, for that at one time he offered two iniu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ryes. Firſt to the Frenche man y<hi rend="sup">t</hi> made the ſame, for whom it had beene ſuffici<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ente that Fraunce had knowen hys do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tinges, &amp; not England alſo to haue bene made partaker of his follyes. Secondly the ill opynion hee ſeemed to haue of his owne countryemen, that amonge the a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bundant choiſe of ſo many excellent Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thematicians, woulde rather publiſhe ſuch a toye, then vſe thaduiſe of ſuche as mighte haue taughte a veritye. For the Booke although it haue fewe lines, yet hath it manye errors &amp; that of all ſortes. <hi>Geometricall, Aſtronomicall, Phyſical, Coſmographicall</hi> and <hi>Hiſtoricall</hi> Firſt in the portrayture of <hi>Caſſiopeia</hi> the very ſtarres are miſtaken, and the new ſtarre miſplaced. For the three other ſtarres
<pb facs="tcp:26242:3"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 101 -->that frame a figure wyth hym of <hi>Geo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mitricianes</hi> commo<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ly called <hi>Rhombus,</hi> are theſe, one of the thirde lighte in her breſte, an other of the ſame lighte in her chayre nighe vnto the thighe of <hi>Caſſio<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>peia,</hi> the thirde in the middle aſcenſe or backe of her Chaire, this beinge of the thirde light alſo, is by him quite miſpla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ced, and in ſteede thereof another little ſtarre of the fifte lighte placed, and the newe ſtarre that is beneath the foote of her ſeate, is there ſituate farre higher. Hee wanteth alſo one ſtarre in the toppe of her chayre, and an other in her foote, and notwythſtandynge he hath clapte in one where neuer anye was, yet wanteth hee one of his nomber, which although hee had neuer redde <hi>Aratus Ptolomey, Copernicus</hi> or other <hi>Mathematicianes,</hi> yet of Poetes as <hi>Palingenius,</hi> he might haue learned howe <hi>Caſſiopeia decem at<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>
                  <expan>
                     <am>
                        <g ref="char:abque"/>
                     </am>
                     <ex>que</ex>
                  </expan> tribus ſtat lucida flammis.</hi> Hee pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceedeth to his obſeruations, and decla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reth this newe ſtarres diſtances from <hi>Alrucuba</hi> commonlye called the <hi>Pole</hi> ſtarre, and another of Queene <hi>Caſſio<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>peia</hi> inferring that ſuch as be ſkilfull in
<pb facs="tcp:26242:3"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 101 -->the doctrine of tria<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>gles <hi>Sphericall,</hi> will ſoone finde his place to be in the ende of ♓ about the <hi>29.</hi> grade, wherby it appea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reth that his own knowledge in <hi>Spheri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>call</hi> triangles was verye ſmall, for ad<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mittinge his owne diſtances true, it fal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leth out in y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> firſt face of ♉, but his true longitude and place in deede, is eſilye by ſighte without Inſtrumente within one degree to be coniectured, of the meaneſt ſcholler in obſeruations <hi>Aſtronomical,</hi> beinge more then that <hi>In ſedis pede,</hi> a little ſtarre harde by hym whoſe longi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tude by <hi>Copernicus</hi> is deliuered <hi>8.</hi> gra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>des. <hi>20.</hi> minutes, and leſſe then that o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther by hym mencioned in <hi>Caſſiopeia</hi> her thighe whoſe longitude is alſo. <hi>10.</hi> grades. This ſtarre therefore being ve<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rye nighe in the meane betweene theſe two, is ſoone founde within <hi>10.</hi> minutes of nyne grades in longitude, makinge accompte as <hi>Copernicus</hi> doth from the little ſtarre in the horne of the Ramme, which in the olde Aſtronomers tyme ſtoode in the very interſection of the line Ecliptike and Equinoctial, but ſithens by the ſtealinge courſe of the ſtarres
<pb facs="tcp:26242:4"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 102 -->fixed, or rather of the earthe as <hi>Coper<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nicus</hi> with better reaſons proueth, is re<g ref="char:EOLunhyphen"/>moued ſince that time <hi>27.</hi> grades <hi>49</hi> minuts, which I haue by certaine Cal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>culatio<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g> found to be <hi>Preceſſio Aequino<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctiorum vera,</hi> for the Natiuitye of oure Sauiour laſt paſt, nyne grades therfore the longitude of this newe ſtarre in the eyghte ſphere by ſighte onely collected, as I haue before declared, vnto y<hi rend="sup">t</hi> nom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ber of the true <hi>Praeceſſion</hi> adioyned, pro<g ref="char:EOLunhyphen"/>duceth <hi>6.</hi> grades <hi>49.</hi> minutes in ♉ for his longitude or place, and therefore I muſe the more that anye man ſhoulde ſo muche erre y<hi rend="sup">t</hi> woulde preſume in a cauſe <hi>Mathematicall</hi> to write, but perhappes his meaninge was y<hi rend="sup">t</hi> this ſtarres righte Aſcention ſhoulde be about that grade, wherein thoughe it be very vnproper to apply the Computation of right Aſcen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſion to the line <hi>Ecliptike,</hi> yet had his er<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ror bene that way the leſſe, but not con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tented wyth theſe inferioure cauſes be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>inge in deede but <hi>Elementa artis,</hi> hee aſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cendeth to diſcouer a <hi>Parallaxe,</hi> &amp; pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>duceth obſeruations flatte repugnaunt betweene theymſelues. I meane not ſo
<pb facs="tcp:26242:4"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 102 -->much for that hee giueth his new ſtarre ſeuerall diſtances from <hi>Alrucuba</hi> at his greateſt heighte, (which in deede is no<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thinge ſo) but hee attributeth alſo vnto hym hys greateſt <hi>Parallaxe</hi> aboue the <hi>Pole,</hi> and his leſſer vnderneath, whiche is a matter ſo abſurde, as oure <hi>Mathe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maticall</hi> infantes will laughe to ſcorne. And theſe hee ſayth are the principall matters hee noted in hym ſince hys firſt appearau<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ce the <hi>15</hi> of Nouember, wher<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>in his credite may ſomthing be doubted alſo, co<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ſidering others of as good iudge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment as he ſeemeth to bee, obſeruinge y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> ſame figure of <hi>Caſſiopeia</hi> coulde ſee no ſuch ſtarre the <hi>16.</hi> night of the ſame mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neth: His Mathematicall cauſes thus handled he entereth to iudge of y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> effects enſuing, and for diſcouery thereof tran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſlateth the opinions of other writers co<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>
               <g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cerning Comets, which by <hi>Ariſtotle</hi> in his booke of <hi>Meteores</hi> are affyrmed to be in the Region of the ayre, and wythin the concauitye of the Moones <hi>Orbe</hi> in<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gendred, affyrming them to be nouriſhed wyth vapours and reſolutions from the ball of earth and <hi>Occeane,</hi> and therefore
<pb facs="tcp:26242:5"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 103 -->rather to ſignifye then to cauſe ſcarcity and ſterilitye enſuinge, but by this Auc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tors owne <hi>Parallaxis</hi> allowing him his own witneſſes, they giue it to be aboue y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> Moone, as any ma<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g> may know that hath any meane ſight, I ſay not in <hi>Sphaerickes</hi> triangles, but plaine and righte lined, &amp; therefore vnleſſe he will make war with naturall Philoſophers and explode <hi>A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſtotle,</hi> he cannot terme hym a Comet. Alſo Comets are into thre kindes deui<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ded, <hi>Crinitas, Barbatas &amp; Caudatas:</hi> And this ſurelye by any ſound ſight to be wel founde none of them: for thoughe hee do ſuppoſe it hath a tayle recching into the <hi>Orient,</hi> wherevppon hee foundeth hys phantaſticall diuinations. Trulye the ſtarre is troubled wyth no ſuch thinge, howſoeuer his head was at the viewing thereof. Againe whereas hee coniectu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reth by his imagined tayle, that his ef<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fect ſhould fall out in the <hi>Orient</hi> &amp; Eaſt partes of y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> world, he ſeemeth alſo there<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>in to be as ſle<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>der a <hi>Coſmographer,</hi> that knoweth not no part of the worlde to be Eaſt or Weſt ſimplye or of it ſelfe: But the thing he harpeth on and hath belike
<pb facs="tcp:26242:5"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 103 -->harde ſome talke of, as of the <hi>Parallaxe</hi> alſo, is this: Aſtronomers firſt by the ſigne wherein the Comet is, his <hi>Paral<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lele,</hi> his ſituation in reſpect of the inter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſection of the <hi>Horizon</hi> and <hi>Meridian,</hi> his latitude, and by many other meanes alſo pronounce firſt of y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> prouinces wher<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on theyr effect ſhal light<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> and then by the direction of the tayle iudge of the parts of thoſe prouinces and the countryes ad<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ioyninge, and ſo in reſpecte of ſome one place determined, others may be called Eaſt or Weſt, <hi>Occident</hi> or <hi>Orient,</hi> at pleaſure. Againe where he pronounceth horrible effects alway to enſue Comets, Hiſtoryes would haue taught hym that ſometime they promiſe vnto ſome great felicitye, as <hi>Iuſtine</hi> when he ſpeaketh of the Comet at <hi>Methridates</hi> byrth ſayth: <hi>Huius quo<expan>
                     <am>
                        <g ref="char:abque"/>
                     </am>
                     <ex>que</ex>
                  </expan> viri magnitudinem Coe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leſtia portenta nuntiabant,</hi> and at y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> in<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>uaſio<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g> of <hi>Tamberlane,</hi> that famous Cap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tayne that toke the Turke and vanqui<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhed his Empyre (aſcending by militare vertue from baſe eſtate) had alſo a Co<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>met which is noted to ſignifye his felici<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tye. But had al his Phiſicall Collecti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ons
<pb facs="tcp:26242:6"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 104 -->beene true, yet vnfitly are the ſigni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fications of Comets applyed to ſtarres, or <hi>Phaenomena</hi> that are aboute the Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gion <hi>Elementare.</hi> To conclude becauſe you requyre my opinion of the booke &amp; the Authors knowledge &amp;c. For y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> mat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter as ye may perceiue, it is farced ſo ful of errors apparant, that euery one that ſauoureth any thing in the ſciences Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thematical, ſhal ſone finde them. Of the man I cannot iudge but <hi>ab affectu,</hi> and ſo take hys audacity much more then ei<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther his learning, or his deſcretion, that would preſume to put himſelfe in preaſe to tell a tale in preſe<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ce of ſuch a no<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ber of <hi>Geometers, Philoſophers, Aſtronomers Coſmographers,</hi> and that of a matter in part concerninge all theyr ſciences, and proceede ſo weekelye furniſhed. It had beene better for him to haue firſt redde <hi>Eraſmus Apothegmata,</hi> wher he ſhold haue founde howe <hi>Apelles</hi> to a Shoma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ker that preſumed to talke in his ſcience leſt this Prouerbe <hi>Ne ſutor vltra crepi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dam,</hi> which well noted might haue cau<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed this Auctour to content hymſelfe to loke on, and geue others leaue to playe y<hi rend="sup">t</hi>
               <pb facs="tcp:26242:6"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 104 -->part on the <hi>Mathematicall</hi> ſtage.</p>
            <p>His concluſion is not to be diſliked for that it contayneth both piety &amp; veritie, &amp; no doubt it is as he ſayth a forewarning of Gods inſcrutable pleaſure, which wil fall out to be no leſſe ſtraung and myra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>culous in effect, then this ſigne wherby it is forewarned is rare and ſupernatu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rall, I commende therefore herein his modeſtye, that he would not geue iudge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mente whether the ſame ſhoulde happen in Fraunce or els where. For ſurelye it were hard for a man of greater ſcience then hee ſeemeth to bee, ſo to doe: But whereſoeuer any haynous outrage hath bene co<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>mitted, eyther by great or ſmall, heade or foote, they haue as hee trulye collecteth, greate cauſe to ſtande in hor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rour of this myraculous ſigne, as a fore<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>runner of Gods iuſt Iudgemente. And thus exhortinge you to proceede in the paſſinge pleaſaunte ſtudyes of the noble ſciences <hi>Mathematicall</hi> fit onely for fre and noble mindes that ſtoupe not at fil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thy lucre I commit you to the protecti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>no, of the Almightye.</p>
         </div>
      </body>
      <back>
         <div type="colophon">
            <pb facs="tcp:26242:7"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 105 -->
            <p>Jmprinted at London by <hi>Thomas Marſhe.</hi>
            </p>
            <pb facs="tcp:26242:7"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 105 -->
         </div>
      </back>
   </text>
</TEI>
